

# Personal information

Name Cecilie Norrbohm

Email cecilie@norrbohm.com

Mobile number +45 28 40 41 13

Adress Egebovej 6 st. th, 2800 Lyngby



## Customer-centric multimedia design student

Outgoing and hardworking multimedia student who cares about customer experience and personal development. I have a passion for photography and digital design - just in general visuals.

Some of the skills I aquired since starting my education: HTML, CSS, bit of JavaScript, Design Principles, Figma prototyping, SoMe Trends, and much more.

### Work experience

2021 - now Triumph, Shop Assistant

Sales and service

2019 - 2020 Skiinstructor in Austria

Teaching groups and private customers in german, english and danish

2018-2019 Espresso House, Assistant Store Manager

Recruitment, training, ordering and participation in schedule planning

#### **Education**

2020 - 2023 Københavns Erhvervs Akademi -

Multimedie design (international)

2020 SBSSV - (Østrigs skilære uddan-

nelse)

2015 - 2018 STX - Borupgaard Gymnasium

#### Certificates

2020 Digital Marketing course at

Succes Online